Uhhuh.
>> What's up everybody?
>> He won't hit that same.
>> I notice I came in
some something back there got me the
other day. I don't know if it's still
there or not, but
>> you show good contact balance though.
>> That's it. That's it. Good contact.
>> You can't fall in front of the
president.
Hey, is that one of them cowboy readers
though?
>> It's exactly.
>> No, it's water.
>> Not yours. It is.
>> All right, Calvin.
>> All right. Good evening, Calvin Watkins,
Dallas Morning News.
>> Uh, as draft was going on, how surprised
were you to to see the ability to to get
downs there at the 11? Well, uh, we had
high respect for him to be trit and
really felt that others did too. U,
you know, I like those odds that the uh
u the u
I like those odds when you're drafting
when the Mavericks got that center. So,
I tried to beat them with the odds of us
picking downs at this spot was. I still
think they got us by percentage or
point, but we beat some odds there to
have him there.
>> Glass
deals Cowboys. Uh, you you traded up.
Can you just talk about the decisions?
Do you think somebody else going to come
up and get him? We just want to make
sure you got your guy.
>> Yes. Yes, definitely. Uh, he was a prize
for us sitting there. He was a prize for
us sitting there with uh with the fives
without the fives.
uh when it would absolutely cut your
heart out. And I' we've had it done.
I've had it done. I' I was just thinking
of the times that we've been the next
pick and had somebody move up and get
him. And we had every reason to think
that that might be happening and u so uh
wore wore it for uh several minutes
there of well what if there was nobody
there to get him? uh you spent some
fives you didn't need to spin and uh
didn't like that feeling so we spent
them didn't want to lose him.
>> Uh Todd Archer with ESPN. Um can you
talk about Lawrence and how you envision
him fitting in this uh defense with
Christian Parker?
>> Yeah, I think you know we love the
ability to rush the passer. Uh we feel
great about what we have with RG and U
as Araku James Houston, but this guy's
got tremendous upside. His first step
quickness, Todd is elite. Uh the ability
to turn his toe and run the edge, as we
like to call it, uh is we think elite.
And then of course the one thing I love
about the guy is he has a innate ability
to attack the football while he's
attacking the quarterback. And then we
feel like, you know, you need athletic
edge pieces in this defense, in this
division because of the quarterbacks
you're going to see. Jackson Dart, Jaden
Daniels, Jaylen Herz, and uh uh it's
nice to have a guy in house like Coach
Brim that's been around him. Uh but this
is a guy we've been talking about a lot
over the last I'd say week to 10 days.
And uh had him in for a top 30 and uh
really really excited about getting a
chance to get him. Stephen, in 2005, you
had two first round picks. Used them on
defensive players uh in Weir and Spears.
This year moving to a 34 like then you
use two defensive players in Downs and
Lawrence. Is this too much of a stretch
that to think that that was part of the
thought process when you're making the
move?
>> Well, I damn sure hope it works out that
way because that worked out in a very
positive way for us. And uh, of course
that along with the rest of the draft,
which we still got a lot of wood to chop
in terms of the rest of the draft, but I
do think we got uh, two really good
football players that uh, uh, you know,
starting with Christian Parker had a
tremendous vision uh, for what these
guys could do for our defense and uh, I
think that was so important to us that
uh, they could come in here and make a
make a big big difference. Obviously,
Caleb uh, I think uh, DS has a
tons of versatility in terms of uh you
know what he can do for us on the
defensive side of the ball where it's
whether it's playing in the nickel uh
being a corner whether it's playing
safety uh he just brings so much
versatility and you know in a place
where we need it. So, uh, you know, not
to mention what he's going to bring, uh,
in terms of, uh, you know, bringing
culture and leadership and, uh, really
blending in with, uh, you know, some of
the guys that we have, which we feel so
good about that we've added just of late
with Quinn and and Kenny. Uh, you know,
I think we're really starting to, you
know, build it the right way in terms of
the football character and the culture
that, uh, that coach Senheimimer wants
to build around here. And, uh, uh, so
anyway, I do think it's a great start.
Obviously, Lawrence uh has very unique
skills that I think can be a big part of
what we're all about here and uh feel
great about him and uh ready to roll up
our sleeves and go back to work
tomorrow.
>> John Mashoto with the athletic firm.
Well, when did kind of Caleb first get
on your radar and and what stands out
most to you about him?
>> When he was a freshman at Alabama, you
saw him playing and amongst all those
guys, you saw somebody that was
different. Um, and then you get to see
it another year and then you get to go
to Ohio State and he's a
differencemaking type player and we're
very very fortunate to get him and I was
surprised that he was there and you look
at the accolades like when you hear
coach Sabin and people talk about how
smart he is and then you talk about the
importance of that like the other day we
were talking about how a brain works and
how that fits into a defense where you
have a guy that can do that. Um, he's a
multiplier. He's going to make other
people better. So, he was it was very
easy to see and I'm glad he's a cowboy.
>> We had we had a big debate.
>> Well, go ahead and talk to Will and go
ahead. I'm serious.
>> Just Lawrence real quick. Uh just
>> um do you like him regardless of what
your scheme is or do you maybe like him
a little bit more because this fits what
Christian's looking for?
>> Um he's a pressure player so you would
like him in any scheme. I think he adds
value to this scheme because, you know,
the edge rush and some of the things
that he can do, the multiplicity that he
could provide for the defense, but
number one's getting after the passer
with speed um and and athleticism, and
we think he can do that.
>> Nick,
>> Nick Harris, Corar Telegram, uh Downs
during the draft process specifically,
it's one thing to see him on the field,
it's another thing to get him in the
building. What stood out uh when you
guys met with him, whether it be combine
or here on the third? I'll speak but
there everybody should address it
because everybody had their thoughts. Uh
our uh planning and discussion really
focused in on either a corner or safety
that could get in the nickel
and uh he easily was the most obvious
one that could get in the nickel for us
and we dared think that uh he might be
there available for us. So number one
that strategically uh that was very
important. And then just to show you how
things go, we spent
uh we we we had uh one player that we
had a let's say heated discussion
regarding before the draft today and it
was uh whether to the other player went
way earlier than that, but it was
Lawrence or the other player. So, I'm
not going to get involved with the other
player because he's on another team now.
But still, the bottom line is that that
we are really uh uh uh we really had uh
a player in mind that we thought had
tremendous upside that fit us and that
we could accept the downside if there
any on him. And so uh the only thing we
didn't do that we had hoped to do was to
uh maybe take some more chances and let
the decision on Lawrence go for about
eight or 10 more and we trading and
getting more picks so that we could add
a pick player and we all decided and had
it decided for us too because the trade
to our satisfaction wasn't there. So,
uh, uh, we really, we really had these
guys, uh, as far as what they could do
for the defense. And if we were going to
come out of here and not have addressed
every hole that at least a personnel
pitcher there could address after this
draft. Uh we tried real hard to uh get
these two positions as well as uh
something at another position on defense
and we u we've accomplished a lot in
there today. And I will say this, you
know, Caleb in the interview, the cool
thing for us is when you bring, you
know, eight to 10 guys in, Nick, you
kind of figure out who they follow. And
it was very evident that, you know,
Caleb's got that personality, that
demeanor that the guys gravitate to him.
I'm talking about the other players,
other elite players around the country.
And um, you know, we had some fun
competitions that, uh, he ended up
winning. And, uh, it was, uh, cool to
see him, uh, in that environment. and
you see his personality and you can see
why he was able to play at such a high
level as a freshman at Alabama because
he's wired the right way.
>> When you guys gave up those two fifth
round picks, were was it kind of a
situation at 20 where you were maybe
maybe seeking a trade back to try to
pick up more capital or did it just kind
of fall in your lap?
>> I think it was both. I mean, I think
it's always nice. we felt like we might
could trade back a little and you know
we obviously uh the guy we would have
picked there we ended up picking three
pick picks later it worked out for us
but we also had some other good football
players that we had targeted that we
could live with and uh just feeling like
picking up those two fours after giving
up the two fives was a uh you know was a
big uh you know was a big deal for us.
So, uh, I'd say both. Uh, we felt like
we could still get our guy there, uh,
where we got him at 23. And, you know,
obviously to pick up back up the draft
capital that we'd given up, uh, was a
big deal. I mean, it actually improved
our situation in terms of turning two
compensatory fives into two fours.
>> It's more fun uh, getting football
players when you got two number ones.
We've had it happen and it's just more
it's a little more interesting.
>> We've got to do this all the time.
>> Tommy Dallascowboys.com. Stephen, you
mentioned turning the two fives into two
fours. Uh how enticing is that? And is
that something that you can maybe
picture trying to pick up another day
two pick like you guys mentioned the
other day?
>> Yeah, I mean it's uh you know what we
don't want to do is give up because we
just don't feel that way
philosophically. You don't want to be
giving up three and four football
players for one player. So, uh, you
know, that part of it is a challenge.
Uh, but, uh, obviously to have draft
capital is helpful. Uh, but still, uh,
you know, it'll be a challenge to, you
know, get into that second round based
on where we sit right now with our picks
and not unless you're willing to give
up, you know, a handful of picks for one
player. And that becomes a uh you know
something that's a challenge for us
because philosophically we don't
necessarily think that's the the perfect
thing to do. Would we totally rule it
out? Absolutely not. We don't ever rule
out anything.
>> Will you mentioned the other day that
that depth in this class is second to
fifth rounds having two more fourth
round picks. What can that do for this
roster?
>> I think you you're going to add quality
players competition. We're going to
strengthen the competition for roster
spots on this roster. And if you
increase the competition, coach
Shenheimer increases the competition
that makes the makes your team stronger
top to bottom.
>> Patrick.
>> Hey guys, Patrick over Dallas
Cowboys.com.
When it comes to Caleb DS, obviously you
guys are excited to have him rightfully
so. You guys have been kind of busy
tonight, so I'm not sure that you know,
but Darren Woodson, he went to social
media and he celebrated the pick. What
does it say for a kid like Caleb DS to
come into this organization and see a
legend like Darren Woodson celebrate his
addition?
>> Just tells you about the young man and
the impact that other people can see his
impact on the field as well as off the
field when you get him on the stage. And
he talks about his reasoning why, you
know, and then you see him play
football. That's what you want on your
team.
>> And for you, Sean, he obviously talked
about culture building and Caleb DS
being in that mold and fitting that that
mold. When you look at Caleb DS adding
him to a defense now led by Christian
Parker and in a back field that has like
a Jaylen Thompson and then the leader
that he could be in that football
acument. What can this Cowboys secondary
and just defense as a whole be in 2026?
Especially looking quickly to rebuild
over 2025.
>> Yeah. Well, I think it starts with with
that. You know, we wanted to add guys
like JT PJ Lock to the secondary. You
get a guy like Caleb DS. Uh he falls to
where you can get him at 11. You know,
one of the top rated guys on our board.
Uh you notice the command and the
communication that he has, the control
of that defense at Ohio State. He did it
at Alabama. Uh it gives you the
flexibility. You're going to have moving
pieces how we want to play the safeties
and do different things. And um we feel
like the one thing we know for sure is
that Caleb will be down in the box and
he'll be lurking and he'll be blitzing
and he'll be filling B and C gaps. And
um you know, he's one of those tools
that you know when you game plan for a
guy like that, you have to be aware of
where he is because he can do so many
things well. He can blitz well. He can
fill the run well. He can cover really
well. But it's not just that, Patrick.
It's his control and command of the
defense. This guy drove the defense at
Ohio State. He made all the calls, made
all the checks, and it was really,
really cool. Uh, talking to Matt
Patricia, some of the guys we reach out
to to hear them talk about it was
immediate. It was not, oh, it took a
little while. It was immediate.
>> Kenny,
>> James Slater, NFL Network. uh ESPN came
on and said there was a 12% chance that
Caleb DS would be there. What was the
realistic percentage you guys had for
him and who's nudging who that here you
are at 12, we need to pick up the phone,
try to get something done for 11. Can
you walk me through that process or how
that played out in the draft room?
>> Well, I tell you, we we thought it was a
long shot that that he would drop to
there. I mean, he wasn't one of the guys
that we felt like would drop. He was
obviously somebody we'd be jumping up
and down if he was there. And I would
say all of us were tapping everybody
saying, "Hey, we need to we need to
think about this." And that's why we
were willing to, you know, give up two
fives to move one spot to uh secure it.
>> Yeah. The real tester is uh we're there.
Are they going to keep him? Are they
going to not draft him who we traded
with? they weren't or they wouldn't have
been on the phone really talking with us
if that's who they were gonna pick. So
what could happen is what has happened
at least in my experience double
handfuls of time is somebody trades
right up in front of you and gets you a
player and that was it pure and simple.
We bought big time insurance. We think
that much of him said man here he is in
our hands. We got him. let's let's go
ahead and spend it and uh come back
around and get it back another way. But
we bought a big-time insurance policy
that somebody wasn't sitting there ready
to trade up in front of us.
>> My next one real quick was that uh Caleb
talked about playing putt putt with you
in your office, Shotty. How do you
initiate a game of putt putt with a
prospect and what do you learn about
someone like that when you're going
through just like a simple little game
and interacting with them in a
competitive way? Well, he talked about
that he had just started playing and
yeah, he's very competitive. Like I
said, the night before he had won the
game of knockout that we played with all
the guys. And so when he started saying
that he was new to golf, I thought for
sure I could beat him. Uh and I didn't.
But you know, again, it's you want to
get these guys in an environment where
it's not just a coach sitting across
from a player. You want to get them to
be their true authentic self. And um I
say this very humbly, he beat me and uh
he reminded me of that tonight on the
phone which uh kind of sucked but uh it
uh it shows you a lot. I mean here's a
guy coming into an environment he's
spending time with the head coach and
the Joneses and Will Mcclelay and um to
uh be able to be that comfortable uh in
an environment where he's looking around
at this amazing facility. It was really
cool to see uh him uh just be who he
was.
>> Did he tell you what his handicap is?
>> Uh he's not very good. He didn't tell me
what it was, but he say he's not very
good. He say he's new to the game. So,
>> Scott Dixon with the AP. This is for
whichever one of you all would like to
address it. In the portal era, stay
portal era. Staying four years at one
school seems unusual. How much of that
is a factor when you're talking about a
guy that's stayed at UCF all four years?
>> It's part of it. It's one of the things
we talk about when you talk about the
character and where they're from and d
what happens. You talk about the
situations. Yes, he was at the he was
offered more money to go different
places and he decided to stay there. You
ask him what his reasoning is and it
tells you a little bit about the player.
So that was something that was into
consideration too. We do have to think
about it and it is something that we
discuss.
>> Shotty, you were not here in 2020 when
CD fell to these guys. What was your
reaction when he's when Caleb is still
there and still there and still there?
Uh, I think the cool thing was how
swiftly, you know, these guys to my left
acted and like I said, we had a high
grade on this guy. We think he's a
multiplier. Uh, we think the versatility
that he brings to the defense is
incredible and uh, how quickly these
guys reacted and so we have a chance to
go get what we think is a difference
maker and uh, it was very surgical.
I asked Shotti to make a list when he
goes home tonight or tomorrow night. U
and I want you to make a list uh who you
think you're going to be sick to your
stomach that we didn't get into next
week. Make that list right now. And of
course, obviously, he was second on the
list and uh it didn't have it in in
order, but the point is you put four of
them on there and he was one of the four
that uh come Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
and you come out here because we've been
looking atund and some 200, 300 players,
there's not going to be but about four
or five of them out here that we drafted
and then we'll have some free agents. It
isn't it isn't what you see in the
draft. It's what you end up with that
you're going to build a team around out
there. And so you've got to kind of look
ahead and say, "Well, I'll be sick if we
don't have him or can I live with it?"
And uh he was on your uh can't live with
>> he was
>> if he had a chance to get him. I
couldn't live without getting him.
>> Would have been disappointed, but he's a
cowboy.
>> Joe White.
>> Joe White Dallas News. Brian, the way
you talked about Kale Downs and the way
that people gravitate to him and it kind
of sounds like how you talked about
Tyler Booker last year in the pre-draft
process. I'm just curious how much did
maybe those interactions with Tyler
Booker and how you guys looked at Caleb
Downs kind of mirror each other a year
later.
>> It's interesting, Joe. Like the one of
the I did not talk to Tyler about um
Caleb, but my phone started blowing up.
We made the selection of Caleb and the
very first text I got was from Tyler
Booker and he was ecstatic. He's like,
"This guy is different." And so you guys
all know how much we love TBook and what
he's brought to this this team and this
offense and we expect the the same thing
from Caleb.
>> And then Stephen News broke before the
night that George Pickins intends to
sign his franchise which would open up
the possibility to be moved if if
possible. Has anything changed in your
guys' expectations that he'll be a
cowboy in 2026?
>> Nothing. We have no intention of moving
George. It obviously uh you know in our
mind we're fired up about it that he's
ready to come in here and sign his
tender and in our mind that means go to
work. Now you know we'll see. And uh but
no, you know, so far everything's been
outstanding. Uh our communication with
George, coach Shottenheimr, Jerry, our
communication with David Mulligetta has
been very cordial and upbeat. So, uh,
we've got every reason in the world to
believe that, uh, you know, hopefully
he's ready to go to work and, uh, but we
have zero intention of moving George
Pickkins.
Todd
>> S of the Athletic Brian, uh, we don't
get to talk to Christian Parker tonight,
but just curious, um, we've asked you a
lot about Caleb DS. What What is, you
know, for Christian Parker with the
defensive backs background and
everything, what is the vision that he
shared of how how excited was he about
getting Caleb DS? Yeah, I I think it
goes to I've talked about side of the
versatility, but you're talking about a
guy that we we see um playing multiple
spots. You know, starting point for him
is going to be playing nickel for us. Um
you get a guy like that that that is
that physical and that athletic and he's
got the ability to cover receivers and
tight ends and also play the run and
more importantly drive the defense and
make the calls. Um but he he also can do
multiple other things. And uh you know
the the biggest thing that CP said to me
is actually funny, but um when we got
Caleb, he told me, Jerry, he said, "Hey,
uh now I'll buy a house." So uh he
hasn't bought a house yet. He's been
busy. He's been grinding on film, but uh
getting a guy like Caleb made him
comfortable. I don't think he's bought
it yet, but in the next couple days, he
said he's ready to buy a house.
>> And he's got a unique way. He does this
thing where he messages you. He He's
trying to get you to think his thoughts.
So he's been sending me pictures of
Caleb and even Malachi all week. So
>> on that
>> he just sends me sends me pictures of
the player just doing something.
>> It means that he really likes him.
>> Yeah. Just send it in the morning so
it's on your mind. Every morning he
would be on your mind.
>> Wells into pictures.
>> Oh
>> little manifestations. Yeah. Like if the
more I talk the more I talk about Caleb
DS and Malachi Lawrence, the more these
guys to my left will make those
decisions. Uh Jerry, on on the
conference call with us, both players
mentioned they don't have to pay state
income tax. Is that is that something
that you sell them on, pitch them on? Do
you make sure the prospects that you
visit know that?
>> Uh almost across the board, no agent
will recognize the Texas sales tax uh
advantage.
And of course, I like to point out that
uh that's just not thinking. If you
don't realize that if you make it in
Texas, different making it in New York.
>> I will say this, that's the benefit of
NIL. These guys are now paying taxes and
so they understand it when they uh
aren't going to be paying state taxes.
>> Garrett Odell, CBS Sports. Jerry, you
talked about kind of realizing when
Jordan Lewis was gone, just the value of
that nickel spot. How much was that on
your mind down here?
>> Very much. I've been brainwashed over
how bad we need a nickel around here.
this whole spring and summer. So uh
really have and uh uh it's it is a big
thing for us and uh uh we had looked for
combinations as I said earlier was it
going to be a corner nickel or was it
going to be a safety nickel? We didn't
know it was going to be quarterback of
the defense nickel and that's what you
got here. And so that's that's what had
us all on our feet when it got close is
my goodness, look what we can, as Shotti
just outlined what it can be. But Will,
I don't think it's out of bounds at all
to say, boy, we went into this thing
nickel oriented this time on terms of
>> of I'm going to say my past and looking
at cover corners or looking at safeties
or safeties that free safeties, strong,
all of that. Uh this was one that uh uh
really puts a premium on the fact that
uh we feel very good about what he does
for us at that spot and these guys are
making that a cornerstone of the had it
right up there with pressure player
right there with pressure players when
it came to okay guys let's position rate
them which would be the biggest impact.
>> You said quarterback and defense I don't
mean to jump in. Is he the could be the
green dot? No, it'll probably be one of
the linebackers, but he the nickel is
going to make a ton of calls. He's going
to drive the communication. He's just he
handles all the change of strength
motions whether we travel, whether we
don't. Um, but what you love about what
he does, Clarence, as you see it on the
film at Ohio State. Not only does he
speak, but he's not asking for anybody
else's opinion. He's making the call and
it's what you're doing.
>> Yeah.
>> Kevin Sharon from Dallas Morning News.
Jerry, is uh is Caleb the best safety
you've granted since uh Woodson?
>> Well, u I'll tell you, we u you know,
Darren had uh played linebacker and then
went back safe. I don't think we could
have imagined the impact that Darren
Woodson would have had on that team.
Now, there's some others
>> that that and we had a Roy Williams come
in and play with, but Darren
>> uh through the years
uh had such a leadership quality. And
what I would point to anybody that is
entering the NFL as Roy Williams as I
mean not Roy Williams, but certainly as
Woodson as an example, look at what he
is after football. Now, that's
impressive. And uh but it's the same
logic, same rationale, same judgment. Uh
leader, leader by example. Uh and then
of course he outworked everybody. So uh
he'd be a he he get Roy Woodson, I mean
Darren Woodson out of him, we'll should
really put a red letter around this day.
Yeah.
>> But I I can't say enough about how that
would uh remind me of that. Let me say
this. No compunction whatsoever in my
mind about taking after doing all the
trading we've done to get these picks
and we have and we've taken some uh
lumps for having these extra picks and
the whole deal that got us here. I
couldn't be more rewarded than have
Downs with one of those picks come in
here because he is a big time. He co
covers a lot of ground other than just
the position we're going to have him on
a defensive play. So, I really did have
a big good inside feeling when we were
able to get a player like that with the
fruits of our labor
>> extra picks. Jonah Jab, WFAA. Jerry, at
what point in the top 10, or I guess
this for any of you, at what point in
the top 10 did you kind of perk up and
think we might be able to get to get
Caleb? Was there a stage there in the
top five?
>> When we got down to the just one left to
we were trying to trade, we were really
working trades all along from the get-go
there in the first round. Uh but uh I
really wouldn't have bet the house.
Well, I didn't. We didn't. We gave two
fives to simply make sure that nobody
would come up ahead of us. We really
knew they weren't going to take him. And
that just shows you really in so many
ways. Uh you say, "Well, uh they're not
going to take him or you wouldn't be
going through all this arduous trading."
But there he was still sitting there.
Well, what what gets you there? Again, I
say it's happened. Somebody just steps
in there and offers them a big three.
Next thing you know, Downs is gone. And
so that really was a very conscious
decision to trade those two fives to be
sure we had him. And we felt pretty good
they weren't going to take him.
>> Was there an attempt to go up earlier in
the top 10 tonight?
>> Uh,
>> we had conversations.
>> Yeah. But
>> those fell apart.
>> But u u he was a he would have been I
think it's fair to say that
him and one other would have been the
only reason to go up
>> for us.
>> Fair. I bet it's kind of fair.
>> Yes.
>> I think it was him and one other
>> were the only we said we're not going
uppecially once he's not still there.
>> Top five picks went.
>> Yeah. I guess I mean was there a player
in that top five when they went did that
kind of change the the mindset of downs
and they fall to us or foul
>> well the offensive guys going got early
help
>> the receivers it it changed the math a
little bit and so the percentages
changed what based on what other people
did but people can still come up and get
a very quality player so that's why we
were you know biting our nails. So
>> when we were two picks out with all that
can happen, people coming in and trading
and getting in front of you. When we
were two picks out, I wasn't thinking
12% odds or anything like that. I just
said because everybody's uh pretty much
looking, we've got to assume that
there's have evaluated him and have
talked to the same coaches we talked to
and everybody pretty much uh they're
looking at the same kind of player. And
so you've got to assume that uh he's
probably uh going to be the next one off
the board. But again, that's what
motivated us. We could have said, you
know what, we're down here now. Nobody's
going to come in front of us. So what?
We don't get him. We'll go on down the
road. But that kind of showed you our
excitement of being there with those
kind of odds.
>> Sydney
>> Sydney Staples, D210 Sports. How do you
guys compare Malachi Lawrence to former
Cowboys players? Any similarities with
anyone you have on the team?
>> Um,
you know, last name, uh, Demarcus
Lawrence or some of that. You know,
he's, uh, um, probably got more juice
than Demarcus from a pure speed
standpoint, but the relentless, uh,
method that he goes after the
quarterback reminds you a little bit of
Demarcus there. Um, and I think the
first step quickness, not to say that
he's him, but one of the things that
made, for example, Demarcus Wear a great
rusher is the ability to get off the
ball and turn the corner. This kid has
some of those traits.
>> All righty. Thank you everybody. Thank
you. Thank you.
the out of that.